

Profile

I'm a passionate and motivated programmer with a lot of experience working with data. My formal undergraduate studies in Economics, Philosophy and Electrical Engineering reflect my broad interest in a wide range of academic areas – both in the humanities and STEM – and have provided a foundation for my passion for self-learning.

Employment History

PhD Candidate, Monash Univerity, Melbourne

OCTOBER 2018 - PRESENT

- Developing Deep Learning based algorithms in Python to improve generalisation of Artificial Intelligence agents to unseen and/or varying environments
- Worked extensively with PyTorch, Numpy, Linux and Git

Teaching Associate, Monash University, Melbourne

MARCH 2019 - NOVEMBER 2021

• Facilitating classes and teaching content for fourth year Computer Vision (ECE4076) and first year electronics (ENG1002)

Research Assistant, QuantEcon (https://quantecon.org/), Canberra

APRIL 2017 - DECEMBER 2021

- Maintaining and debugging Python and Julia code for the QuantEcon learning content, using test-driven development
- Contributing to new content, including interactive Jupyter notebooks

Technical Services Analyst, Experian Asia Pacific, Melbourne

DECEMBER 2015 - FEBRUARY 2017

- Automating internal data processing with Python and SQL
- Running targeted Facebook ads with A/B testing to measure impact
- Building programs using Python, SQL and the Facebook SDK to assist the sales team

Education

Graduate Diploma of Economics, Australian National University, Canberra

FEBRUARY 2017 - NOVEMBER 2017

WAM 80.25

Bachelor of Engineering with Honours and Bachelor of Arts, Monash University, Melbourne

FEBRUARY 2010 - NOVEMBER 2015

WAM 73.2

References

References available upon request

Details

Elsternwick 3185, Melbourne Australia 0412956747 ajhebblewhite@gmail.com

Links

LinkedIn

Skills

Python

Machine Learning

Data Analysis

SQL

JavaScript

Web Development

Econometrics